alphaimports.com 2008-06-15

# Privacy policy - check the privacy

|  |  |  | Help support and information center. |    
---|---  
[« Go to Help Center](http://www.alphaimports.com/help.html)       « Back to previous page Privacy Policy

|   
---  
  
| 

**Privacy Policy**

Alpha Imports NY Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on [http://www.alphaimports.com](http://www.alphaimports.com/). Alpha Imports NY Inc. collects information from our users on our Web site.  
  
---  
You may not copy, give or sell copies to members of the public; perform or display this work to the public or modify this work without the copyright owner's permission.  
**Special Offers and Updates**  
We send all new members a Special Offers. Established members will receive information on special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.   
**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications.   
**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.  
**Third Party Intermediaries**  
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes  
**Security**  
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing’. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to user information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. As well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users’ information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to support@alphaimports.com  
  
**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**  
If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at by emailing our Customer Support at info [at] alphaimports.com. (Or, contact us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below).  
**Choice/Opt-out**  
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to remove in the subject line in the email or email us at : support [at] alphaimports.com (or the user may contact us at to opt-out.)  
  
  Sunday 15 June, 2008   |   6235923 requests since Saturday 15 May, 2004    
---|---  
  
Quick Help Links

Website Features

Find Products

| 

Product Information 

Subscribe

---|---|---|---|---  
  
All our colored gemstones, except Tsavorite, Garnet etc., are "E" (Enhanced) and/or "T" (Treated). In general, some of the enhancement methods used are heating, oiling, filling, with resin agents etc. Some of the treatment methods used are coating, diffusion, dyeing, joban oil, glass filling, irradiation, lasering, etc. We do not know the methods used prior to our purchase from the suppliers since each country uses different methods. If required, we may send the Gemstone(s) to a Gem laboratory for more information prior to your purchase.Products shown are subject to availability.Alphaimports.com is not responsible for and need not honor typographical or pricing errors on the site.  
****All Diamond weight(s) shown in fractions in this website are approximate, with the following weight tolerance: ¼ ct. 0.23-0.27, 1/3 ct. 0.31-0.35, ½ ct.0.48-0.52, ¾ ct.0.73-0.77.** **  
All Contents © 2008 Alpha Imports NY Inc., All Rights Reserved. [_PRIVACY POLICY_](http://www.alphaimports.com/help/privacy-policy.html) [_TERMS AND CONDITIONS_](http://www.alphaimports.com/help/terms-and-conditions.html)  
You may not distribute, modify, display, or sell copies of this work to members of the public without the copyright owner’s permission.   
All of our products are bought as close outs from manufacturers and we describe them on our web site as it was disclosed to us. The Alphaimports.com website and the products and services offered therein are provided "as is" and without warranty of any kind. For any reason if you are not satisfied with the product we have full refund policy. [More...](http://www.alphaimports.com/help/terms-and-conditions.html)
